Isabella Karle and Jerome Karle Papers
Manuscript Division, Library of Congress
- Jerome Karle Papers, 1912-2009 (Box 174-412)
  - Organizations and Institutions, 1941-2009 (Box 222-318)
    - International Union of Crystallography (Box 237)
      - Committee on International Union of Crystallographers Statutes and Bylaws, 1991-1995 (Box 241)
      - Computer output, 1983 (Box 241)
      - Congresso Iberoamericano de Cristalographia, Coimbra, Portugal, 1981, Sept. 21-26 (Box 241)
      - Correspondence, miscellaneous, 1982-1984 (Box 241)
      - Databases, 1981-1984 (Box 241)
      - Ejnar Munksgaard (publisher), 1881-1884, (2 folders) (Box 242)
      - European Crystallographic Committee, 1978-1983, (2 folders) (Box 242)
      - European Physical Society, 1981 (Box 242)
      - Ewald Prize, 1973, 1985-1994, (2 folders) (Box 242)
      - Executive Committee meetings, 1978-1979, (2 folders) (Box 242)
      - Executive Committee meetings, 1980-1986, (7 folders) (Box 243)
      - Executive Committee meetings, 1987 (Box 244)
      - Executive Committee meetings; Finance Committee meetings, 1983-1987, (2 folders) (Box 244)
      - Executive Committee reports, 1972-1987 (Box 244)
      - Fifth European Meeting on Ferroelectricity, Malaga, Spain, 1983, Sept. 26-Oct. 1 (Box 244)
      - Finance Committee, 1980-1982, (3 folders) (Box 244)
      - Finance Committee, 1983-1984, (2 folders) (Box 245)
      - Finance Committee meetings, 1982-1985, (6 folders) (Box 245)
      - Financial crisis, 1981 (Box 245)
      - Financial reports, 1980-1984 (Box 246)
      - General Assembly code of conduct, 1981-1982 (Box 246)
      - General Assembly and International Congress V, Cambridge, England, 1960 (Box 246)
      - General Assembly and International Congress VII, Moscow, Soviet Union, 1966, July 12-21 (Box 246)
      - General Assembly and International Congress VIII, Buffalo, N.Y., Stony Brook, N.Y., Upton, N.Y., Washington, D.C., 1969, Aug. 7-27, (4 folders) (Box 246)
      - General Assembly and International Congress VIII, Buffalo, N.Y., Stony Brook, N.Y., Upton, N.Y., Washington, D.C., 1969, Aug. 7-27, (7 folders) (Box 247)
      - General Assembly and International Congress VIII, Buffalo, N.Y., Stony Brook, N.Y., Upton, N.Y., Washington, D.C., 1969, Aug. 7-27 (Box 248)
      - General Assembly and International Congress VIV, Kyoto, Japan, 1972, Aug. 26-Sept. 7 (Box 248)
      - General Assembly and International Congress X, Amsterdam, Netherlands, 1975, Aug. 7-15, (3 folders) (Box 248)
      - General Assembly and International Congress XI, Warsaw, Poland, 1978, Aug. 3-12, (2 folders) (Box 248)
      - General Assembly and International Congress XI, Warsaw, Poland, 1978, Aug. 3-12, (3 folders) (Box 249)
      - General Assembly and International Congress XII, Ottawa, Canada, 1981, Aug.16-25, (3 folders) (Box 249)
      - General Assembly and International Congress XIII, Hamburg, Germany, 1984, Aug. 9-18, (4 folders) (Box 250)
      - General Assembly and International Congress XIV, Perth, Australia, 1987, Aug. 12-20, (2 folders) (Box 250)
      - General Assembly and International Congress XV, Bordeaux, France, 1990, July 19-28 (Box 250)
      - General Assembly and International Congress XVI, Beijing, China, 1993, Aug. 21-29 (Box 250)
      - General Assembly and International Congress XVII, Seattle, Wash., 1996, Aug. 8-17 (Box 250)
      - General Assembly and International Congress XVII, Seattle, Wash., 1996, Aug. 8-17 (Box 251)
      - General Assembly and International Congress XVIII, Glasgow, Scotland, 1999, Aug. 4-13 (Box 251)
      - Hahn, Theo, 1984-1987 (Box 251)
      - History, 1983 (Box 251)
      - In-house composition, 1980-1981 (Box 251)
      - Intercongress symposium, "Intra- and Intermolecular Forces," University Park, Pa., 1974, Aug. 13-17 (Box 251)
      - Internal Revenue Service, 1984-1988, (2 folders) (Box 251)
      - International Conference on the Application of the Mössbauer Effect, Jaipur, India, 1981, Dec. 14-18 (Box 251)
      - International Conference on Neutron Scattering of Condensed Matter, Hakone-machi, Japan, 1982, Sept. 1-4 (Box 251)
      - International Council of Scientific Unions See also Container 236, same heading; See also Container 275, Advisory Committee for the ICSU (Box 252)
        - Abstracting Board; International Council for Scientific and Technical Information, 1982-1986 (Box 252)
        - Committee on Science and Technology in Developing Countries, 1982-1987 (Box 252)
        - Free circulation, 1985-1996 (Box 252)
        - Miscellany, 1981-1984, (5 folders) (Box 252)
        - Miscellany, 1985-1987, (2 folders) (Box 253)
      - International Institute for Crystallography, proposal, 1980-1984 (Box 253)
      - International Meeting on Accurate Determination of X-ray Intensities and Structure Factors, Cambridge, England, 1968, June 24-28 (Box 253)
      - International School on Material Science and Solar Energy, Egypt, 1983, Mar. 15-30 (Box 253)
      - International School on Synthesis, Crystal Growth and Characterization of Materials for Energy Conversion and Storage, New Delhi, India, 1981, Oct. 12-23 (Box 253)
      - International Specialists School on Crystal Growth, Suzdal', Russia, 1980, Sept. 17-25 (Box 253)
      - International Summer School on Crystallographic Computing, Ottawa, Canada, 1981, Aug. 7-15 (Box 253)
      - International Union of Pure and Applied Chemistry; Interdivisional Committee on Nomenclature and Symbols, 1982-1984 (Box 253)
      - Kato, Norio, 1979-1983 (Box 253)
      - King, J. N., 1979-1993, (5 folders) (Box 254)
      - Kurki-Suonio, K., 1981-1983 (Box 254)
      - Kurki-Suonio, K., 1984-1987, 2003 (Box 255)
      - Long Range Planning Committee, 1981-1983 (Box 255)
      - Manuscript flow, 1981-1984, (2 folders) (Box 255)
      - Mexico, 1981-1984 (Box 255)
      - Miscellany, 1956, 1962, (3 folders) (Box 255)
      - Nominations for Executive Committee and commissions, 1979-1983 (Box 255)
      - Peace; Nuclear war, 1981-1986 (Box 256)
      - Penfold, David, 1981-1985, (2 folders) (Box 256)
      - Polycrystal Book Service, 1982-1986 (Box 256)
      - President's fund, 1978-1984 (Box 256)
      - Publication charge, 1981 (Box 256)
      - Publications fund, 1982 (Box 256)
      - Rasmussen, Svend Erik, 1979-1983 (Box 256)
      - Sagamore VII Conference on Charge, Spin and Momentum Densities, Japan, 1982, Aug. 25-30 (Box 256)
      - Scientific Committee on Problems of the Environment, 1982 (Box 257)
      - Seventh European Crystallographic Meeting, Jerusalem, 1982, Aug. 29-Sept. 3 (Box 257)
      - Shefra Graphics, 1981-1982 (Box 257)
      - Small angle scattering; Schmidt, Paul W., 1981-1983 (Box 257)
      - Subcommittee on the Union Calendar, 1979-1986, (4 folders) (Box 257)
      - Subcommittee on the Union Calendar, 1981-1986, (2 folders) (Box 258)
      - Symposium on Molecular Structure and Biological Activity, Buffalo, N.Y., 1981, Aug. 26-28 (Box 258)
      - Symposium on Crystallography in the Health Sciences, Toronto, Canada, 1981, Aug. 13-14 (Box 258)
      - Symposium on Neutron Scattering, Argonne, Ill., 1981, Aug. 12-14 (Box 258)
      - Symposium on Fundamental Aspects of Material Science in Space, Ottawa, Canada, 1982, May 25-28 (Box 258)
      - Unesco, 1984-1984 (Box 258)
      - Unit contribution, 1982-1983 (Box 258)
      - Woolfson, Michael Mark, 1981-1986 (Box 258)
      - Workshop, "Crystallography of Molecular Biology," Erice, Italy, 1982, June 7-19 (Box 258)
      - World Directory of Crystallographers, 1965, 1984-1986 (Box 258)
      - World Directory of Crystallographers, 1990 (Box 259)
    - International Physicians for the Prevention of Nuclear War, 1988 (Box 259)
    - Linus Pauling Exhibition Advisory Committee, 1999 (Box 259)
    - Mathematical Association of America, 1973, 1979 (Box 259)
    - Millenium Committee of New York, 1997-1999 (Box 259)
    - National Academy of Sciences (Box 259)
      - Arts Advisory Committee (Box 259)
        - Exhibits and concerts, 1981-2001, (5 folders) (Box 259)
        - Meetings, 1995-2001, (10 folders) (Box 260)
        - Miscellany, 1993-2002 (Box 260)
      - Auditing Committee, 1980-1981, (3 folders) (Box 260)
      - Auditing Committee, 1982-1984, (5 folders) (Box 261)
      - Biographical information requests, 1976-1989, 1998 (Box 261)
      - Board on International Organizations and Programs, 1977-1980 See also Container 238, same heading, (2 folders) (Box 261)
      - Chemistry section (Box 261)
        - Award in Chemical Sciences, 1988-1994 (Box 261)
        - Award for Chemistry in Service to Society, 1989-1990 (Box 261)
        - Award for Chemistry in Service to Society, 1992 (Box 262)
        - Ballots and nomination procedures, 1985-1988 (Box 262)
        - Class Membership Committee, 1988-1991 (Box 262)
        - Committee on Chemistry and Federal Policy, 1977-1986, (6 folders) (Box 262)
        - Committee on Underrepresented Disciplines, 1987-1989 (Box 262)
        - Correspondence, 1988-1993, (2 folders) (Box 262)
        - Elections and membership, 1976-1991, (7 folders) (Box 263)
        - Elections and membership, 1992-2008, undated, (7 folders) (Box 264)
        - Hofbauer Brown, Mary, 1988-1992 (Box 264)
        - Incoming chairperson, 1988 (Box 265)
        - Kellogg Foundation challenge grant, 1987-1990 (Box 265)
        - Meetings, 1987-1991, (4 folders) (Box 265)
        - Miscellany, 1976-1995, (4 folders) (Box 265)
        - Miscellany, 1996-2009, (2 folders) (Box 266)
        - Revision of section rules, correspondence, 1987-1988 (Box 266)
        - Sherman, Elizabeth, 1988-1991 (Box 266)
        - Wiberg, Kenneth B., 1988-1989 (Box 266)
      - Committee on Human Rights (Box 266)
        - Correspondence, 1976-1983, (4 folders) (Box 266)
        - Correspondence, 1984-1992, (7 folders) (Box 267)
        - Correspondence, 1992-1997, (8 folders) (Box 268)
        - Correspondence, 1998-2005, (5 folders) (Box 269)
        - Guatemala, 1991-1992, (2 folders) (Box 269)
        - Meetings, 1991-1992, (3 folders) (Box 270)
        - Meetings, 1993-1994, (4 folders) (Box 271)
        - Meetings, 1995-1996, (4 folders) (Box 272)
        - Meetings, 1997-1998, (4 folders) (Box 273)
        - Meetings, 1999-2001, (2 folders) (Box 274)
        - Members and staff, 1996 (Box 274)
        - Vietnam Human Rights Day, 1998-2001 (Box 274)
      - Election and initial correspondence, 1976 (Box 274)
      - Letter to Members (publication), 1976-1979 (Box 274)
      - Letter to Members (publication), 1989-1996 (Box 275)
      - National science education standards, 1998 (Box 275)
      - News releases, 1977-1980, 1988-1989 (Box 275)
      - Proceedings of the National Academy of Sciences of the United States of America submissions, 1981-1989 (Box 275)
      - Soviet Union, 1988 (Box 275)
      - Supreme Court amici curiae, 1997 (Box 275)
    - National Research Council (Box 275)
      - Ad Hoc Panel on Interatomic Distances, 1969 (Box 275)
      - Ad Hoc Panel on Major Instrumentation Needs for Research in Chemistry and Biological Chemistry, 1976, (2 folders) (Box 275)
      - Advisory Committee for the International Council of Scientific Unions See also Container 236, ICSU; See also Container 252, ICSU (Box 276)
        - Correspondence, 1986-1987, (6 folders) (Box 276)
        - Correspondence, 1988-1989, (4 folders) (Box 277)
        - International Council of Scientific Unions General Assembly, 1984, (3 folders) (Box 277)
        - International Council of Scientific Unions General Assembly, 1984-1988, (6 folders) (Box 278)
        - Meetings, 1986-1987, (4 folders) (Box 279)
        - Meetings, 1988, (2 folders) (Box 280)
        - Miscellany, 1986-1990, (2 folders) (Box 280)
        - Newsletter, 1982-1987 (Box 280)
        - "Report on Fiscal Year 1987 International Convention and Scientific Organizations Contributions Grants to the National Academy of Sciences," 1989 (Box 280)
      - Division of physical sciences, 1954-1958 (Box 281)
      - "Needs and Opportunities for the National Resource for Computaton in Chemistry" (report), 1976 (Box 281)
      - Numerical Data Advisory Board, 1985-1986, (4 folders) (Box 281)
      - Numerical Data Advisory Board, 1987-1990, (9 folders) (Box 282)
    - National Science Teachers Association, 1986-1990 (Box 283)
    - National Science Foundation (Box 283)
      - "Crystallography in Universities, Industry, and Other Research Institutions" (report), 1982 (Box 283)
      - Physical chemistry workshop and report, 1984-1988, (8 folders) (Box 283)
    - Naval Research Laboratory (Box 283)
      - "1985 Review," 1986 (Box 283)
      - 3,3-Bis(azidomethyl)oxetane (BAMO), 1980-1982 (Box 284)
      - AIDS, 1986-1992 (Box 284)
      - Anomalous Scattering of Protein Structures (grant), 1980-1983, (2 folders) (Box 284)
      - Applications for employment, Jerome Karle, 1947-1949, 1961 (Box 284)
      - Argonne National Laboratory collaboration, 2003 (Box 284)
      - Atomic Structure of Reversible Oxygen Carriers (proposal), circa 1980 (Box 284)
      - Auger electrons, 1990-1991 (Box 284)
      - Bioluminescence, 1997 (Box 284)
      - Biomedical Committee; Radiobiomedical Committee, 1972-1974, (5 folders) (Box 285)
      - Böhlke, Rainer, 1993-1994 (Box 285)
      - Capital purchase program, 1992-2002, (2 folders) (Box 285)
      - Category 6.1 program, 1967 (Box 285)
      - Central computing facility, circa 1988 (Box 285)
      - Chemical Research and Development Center, Aberdeen Proving Ground, Md., 1984-1985 (Box 285)
      - Combining 6.1 and 6.2 programs, 1993 (Box 286)
      - Commanding officer, 1998-1999 (Box 286)
      - Computer information, 1959-1962 (Box 286)
      - Contracting information, 1991-1994 (Box 286)
      - Contracts and proposals, 1990-1996, (3 folders) (Box 286)
      - Contributions to national security, 1992 (Box 286)
      - Cray X-MP, 1988-1993 (Box 286)
      - Dilute Chemical Surety Material Program, 1984 (Box 287)
      - Distinguished lecture series, 1990 (Box 287)
      - Energetic Materials Program, 1980-1981 (Box 287)
      - Energy Research Panel, 1973-1975, (4 folders) (Box 287)
      - Environmental Protection Agency, asbestos, 1973 (Box 287)
      - Executive Council, 2000-2007 (Box 287)
      - Explosives, 2003-2006 (Box 287)
      - Explosives Safety Committee, 1994-1995 (Box 287)
      - Federal awards criteria, 1982-1987 (Box 287)
      - "Final Report of the Working Group on Federal Laboratory Personnel Issues," 1984-1985 (Box 287)
      - Financing and funding, 1973-1978, 1987-1990, (7 folders) (Box 288)
      - Financing and funding, 1991-1995, (7 folders) (Box 289)
      - Financing and funding, 1996-2007, (3 folders) (Box 290)
      - "Firsts" at the Naval Research Laboratory, 1967-1971 (Box 290)
      - Five-year plan, 1976, 1990, (2 folders) (Box 290)
      - Focus area review, 1997 (Box 290)
      - "Future of the Naval Research Laboratory" (presentation), 1989 (Box 290)
      - Future program, 1958-1961 (Box 290)
      - "Good words," 1981-1993 (Box 291)
      - High performance computing, 1992-1998, (7 folders) (Box 291)
      - High performance computing, 1997-2008, (3 folders) (Box 292)
      - Honorarium information, 1986 (Box 292)
      - Interagency support agreement, 1980-1981 (Box 292)
      - International Union of Pure and Applied Chemistry, 1986 (Box 292)
      - International Business Machines Corp. (IBM), 1997 (Box 292)
      - Investigation of the Structure of Heparin (proposal and report), 1974-1977, (2 folders) (Box 292)
      - Karasek, John J., 1994 (Box 293)
      - Kaufman, Joyce, proposals and reports, 1979-1981, (2 folders) (Box 293)
      - Kunz, Barry, 1982, 1985 (Box 293)
      - Laboratory for the Structure of Matter (Box 293)
        - Annual review, 1968-1977, (2 folders) (Box 293)
        - Discussion, 1973 (Box 293)
        - Management control; Internal control, 1985-2000, (2 folders) (Box 293)
        - Pre-retreat reviews, 1981-1988, undated, (7 folders) (Box 294)
        - Program reviews, 1992-1997, (4 folders) (Box 294)
        - Program reviews, 1998, (2 folders) (Box 295)
        - Progress, 1974 (Box 295)
        - Research and development accomplishments, 2000-2004 (Box 295)
        - Research program presentation, 1988, 2003, (2 folders) (Box 295)
        - Task area narratives, 1975-1977, 1984-1989, (5 folders) (Box 295)
        - Task area narratives, 1990-1994, (5 folders) (Box 296)
        - Task area narratives, 1993, mss85507_215_004; mss85507_215_005
        - Triennial review, 2002, June 12, mss85507_215_006
        - Triennial review, 2002 (Box 296)
      - Matsuura, Toyoaki, 1997 (Box 296)
      - Mechanics and atomistics of mechanical behavior, 1991-1993 (Box 296)
      - Memoranda, 1969-1985, (2 folders) (Box 296)
      - Memoranda, 1985-1998, (7 folders) (Box 297)
      - Memoranda, 1999-2007 (Box 298)
      - Merit pay, 1980-1982 (Box 298)
      - Microstructure workshop; Miller, Richard; Dickinson, Charles, 1985-1986 (Box 298)
      - Mihill, Arthur, 1991 (Box 298)
      - Miscellany, 1947-1992, (4 folders) (Box 298)
      - Miscellany, 1993-2008, undated, (7 folders) (Box 299)
      - Neuroscience research option, 1987 (Box 299)
      - National Bureau of Standards, 1949, 1958 (Box 299)
      - National Institutes of Health (Box 299)
        - Computing costs, 1972-1975 (Box 299)
        - Funding, 1996-1998 (Box 300)
      - Naval Research Laboratory Awareness Day, 1990, Nov. 7 (Box 300)
      - Navy Meritorious Civilian Service Award, 1986-1988 (Box 300)
      - Navy National Nanotechnology Initiative, 2000 (Box 300)
      - Navy Review of Subelement General Physics, 1975 (Box 300)
      - Navy science and technology program, 2004-2007, undated (Box 300)
      - "Navy's Corporate Laboratory," 1997-2002 (Box 300)
      - "Navy's Corporate Laboratory," digital files, 1997-2002, mss85507_215_007
      - Nobel laureates lecture, 2001, June 18 (Box 300)
      - Notes from administration, 1999-2005, (3 folders) (Box 300)
      - Notes to Pentagon secretaries, 1998-1999 (Box 300)
      - Office of Technology Assessment, U.S. Congress, 1978 See also Container 387, same heading (Box 300)
      - "Optics at the Naval Research Laboratory" by J. A. Sanderson, 1967 (Box 300)
      - Research projects in biomolecular structure, 1960 (Box 300)
      - Performance evaluations of Jerome Karle, 1947-1980 (Box 300)
      - Performance evaluations of Jerome Karle, 1981-1993, (6 folders) (Box 301)
      - Performance evaluations of Jerome Karle, 1994-2008, undated, (3 folders) (Box 302)
      - Personnel actions and promotions, Karle, 1946-1979, 1989, 1998 For additional material see Container 178, Chair of Science (Box 302)
      - Physiologically Active Materials, Their Structure and Function (proposal), 1973-1974 (Box 302)
      - Planning, 1989-1998 (Box 302)
      - Position descriptions, Karle, 1948-1979, 1994-1996, undated, (2 folders) (Box 302)
      - Postdoctoral fellowships, 1959-1969, 2000-2001, (2 folders) (Box 303)
      - Postdoctoral fellowships and summer faculty programs, 1969, 1980-1982 (Box 303)
      - "Potential protein research," 1996-2002 (Box 303)
      - Prince William Institute, George Mason University, Fairfax, Va. 1995 (Box 303)
      - Proposal for Anti-Cancer Drug Program of the National Cancer Institute, 1973 (Box 303)
      - Protein structure program, 1970-1974 (Box 303)
      - Reports, Office of Naval Research, 1973-1974, 1982-1986, 1992-1996, (4 folders) (Box 303)
      - Reports, Office of Naval Research, 1996-2004, (8 folders) (Box 304)
      - Research options; Patten, F. W., 1980-1981 (Box 304)
      - Research plan, fiscal year 1990, 1989 (Box 304)
      - Robclif Productions, 1992 (Box 304)
      - Rouse, Carl A.; Schrödinger equation, 1966-1968 (Box 304)
      - Safety, 1994-1997 (Box 304)
      - Schindler, A. I., 1977-1980 (Box 305)
      - Senior Executives Association; Senior Executive Service, 1978-2007, (6 folders) (Box 305)
      - Senior management retreat, 1989, Nov. 15-17 (Box 306)
      - Seventy-fifth anniversary of the Naval Research Laboratory (1998), 1998-2003 (Box 306)
      - Small Business Innovation Research program, 1997-1998 (Box 306)
      - Smooth muscle-acting factor (SMAF) chromoatograph, 1974 (Box 306)
      - Specialty materials for underwater acoustics, 1982 (Box 306)
      - Staff positions, 1958-1967 (Box 306)
      - Structural Characterization of Amorphous Boron by Electron and X-Ray Diffraction Techniques (proposal), 1979-1980 (Box 306)
      - Structure of Coal Investigated by X-Ray Electron Diffraction Techniques (proposal), 1976-1979 (Box 306)
      - "Structures that Matter: Methods and Applications," circa 1995 (Box 306)
      - "Study of the Navy's Energy Research Needs- From the Viewpoint of Naval Research Laboratory Involvement," 1974 (Box 306)
      - Summer faculty research programs, 1987-1990 (Box 306)
      - Superintendent's Forum, 1991-1993, (2 folders) (Box 306)
      - Synthesis Facilitation of Biomass Growth Regulators by X-Ray Diffraction Analysis (proposal), 1979 (Box 306)
      - Technical reports, 1952 (Box 307)
      - Ten-year projection, 1974 (Box 307)
      - "Transformation Planning Guidance," 2003 (Box 307)
      - Travel, Karle, 1946-1963, 1985, 2000, (2 folders) (Box 307)
      - Undersecretary precepts, 1992 (Box 307)
      - Underwater Sound Reference Division, Orlando, Fla., 1981-1982 (Box 307)
      - Vekhter, Yanina, 2000-2003 (Box 307)
      - Visiting committee lecture, 1968 (Box 307)
      - Vos, Aafje, 1966-1967 (Box 307)
      - Ward, Keith, 1984-1995, (2 folders) (Box 307)
      - Ward, Keith, 1984-1995 (Box 308)
      - "Waterfall" charts, 2003 (Box 308)
      - Work unit assignment summaries, 1974, 1983-1990, (2 folders) (Box 308)
    - Nova Spes International Foundation, 1987-1997, (3 folders) (Box 308)
    - Organization for Promoting Global Civilization, 1999-2001 (Box 308)
    - Philosophical Society of Washington, 1971-2005 (Box 308)
    - Thomas Jefferson High School, Fairfax, Va., 1995-2001 (Box 309)
    - United States of America Committee for Crystallography, 1953-1956, 1963-1970, (6 folders) (Box 309)
    - United States of America Committee for Crystallography, 1971-1974, (9 folders) (Box 310)
    - United States of America Committee for Crystallography, 1974-1976, (7 folders) (Box 311)
    - United States of America Committee for Crystallography, 1977-1983, (7 folders) (Box 312)
    - United States of America Committee for Crystallography, 1981-1989, (3 folders) (Box 313)
    - University of Maryland, teaching files (Box 313)
      - Advanced calculus, 1959-1962, (3 folders) (Box 313)
      - Advanced mathematics for physicists and engineers, 1960-1961, (2 folders) (Box 313)
      - Advanced mathematics for physicists and engineers, 1960-1961 (Box 314)
      - Crystallography, 1950-1967, (2 folders) (Box 314)
      - Electrodynamics, 1963-1964, (3 folders) (Box 314)
      - Introduction to modern algebra, 1960-1961, (2 folders) (Box 315)
      - Miscellany, 1950-1951, 1957-1968, undated, (5 folders) (Box 315)
      - Quantum mechanics, 1962-1963, (3 folders) (Box 316)
    - University of Michigan (Box 316)
      - Correspondence, 1986-2001 (Box 316)
      - Department of Chemistry Alumni and Industrial Advisory Council, 1992-1993, (4 folders) (Box 316)
      - Department of Chemistry Alumni and Industrial Advisory Council, 1994-2003, (7 folders) (Box 317)
      - National Committee for the Rakham Annual Fund, 1988-1997 (Box 317)
    - World Constitution and Parliament Association, 1988-1995 (Box 317)
    - World Federation of Scientists, 2002-2005 (Box 317)
    - World Innovation Foundation, 1997-1999 (Box 317)
    - World Innovation Foundation, 1997-2008, undated, (6 folders) (Box 318)
  - Subject File, 1912-2009 (Box 318-412)